const e=[{id:1,type:"radio",title:"Layer Outlier",question:"Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model",options:["Network Interface Card (NIC)","Router","IP Address","Cable"],answer:"IP Address"},{id:2,type:"radio",title:"Goodbye",question:"Which TCP flag is used to gracefully terminate a session between two systems",options:["PIN","FIZ","FIN","SYN","END","ACK","RST"],answer:"FIN"},{id:3,type:"radio",title:"What’s the Point?",question:"Which statement correctly characterizes the functions of the OSI Model",options:["A method of describing the functions of a networking system to allow communication","A physical device used to connect computers to a network","A protocol used for encrypting network traffic","A type of network cable used in data centers"],answer:"A method of describing the functions of a networking system to allow communication"},{id:4,type:"checkbox",title:"Presentation Powers",question:"Which common services occur at the presentation layer of the OSI Model?",options:["encryption","compression","routing","IP addressing","packet switching","MAC addressing"],answer:["encryption","compression"]},{id:6,type:"radio",title:"",question:"Which device or service would not operate at the physical layer of the OSI Model?",options:["Network Interface Card","IP Address","Switch","Hub"],answer:"IP Address"},{id:7,type:"radio",title:"Communicate with who?",question:"Which type of communication would be analogous to a half duplex transmission",options:["a group chat where only one person can send a message at a time","two people using walkie-talkies","a one-way radio broadcast","two people talking on the phone at the same time"],answer:"two people using walkie-talkies"},{id:9,type:"checkbox",title:"Guaranteed Delivery",question:"If you needed to be certain that your data transmission are being received, which type of connection(s) and/or protocol(s) should be used",options:["connection-oriented","TCP","connectionless","UDP","broadcast","multicast"],answer:["connection-oriented","TCP"]},{id:10,type:"radio",title:"I spy MTU size",question:"Which command can be used to determine the MTU optimal size?",options:["traceroute","ping","arp","ifconfig","hostname","nslookup","ipconfig"],answer:"ping"},{id:11,type:"checkbox",title:"App Lyaer All-Stars",question:"Which protocol(s) operate at the application layer of the OSI Model",options:["SMTP","HTTP","FTP","TCP","UDP","SSH","ICMP","PIMP"],answer:["SMTP","HTTP","FTP","SSH"],description:`**Correct**
- SMTP (simple mail transfer protocol)
- HTTP (hyper-text transfer protocol)
- FTP (file transfer protocol)
- SSH (secure-shell protocol)

**Incorrect**
- TCP (transmission control protocol): Transport layer
- UDP (user datagram protocol): Transport layer
- ICMP (internet control message protocol): Network layer
- PIMP (not a real protocol): if you fell for this you might not make it
`},{id:12,type:"checkbox",title:"Traffic cop",question:"Which type of traffic management service(s) occurs at the network layer of the OSI Model",options:["routing","error detection","flow control","segmentation","multiplexing"],answer:["routing"],description:`**Correct**
- Routing: The network layer is responsible for determining the best path for data to travel across networks.

**Incorrect**
- Error detection: usually performed at the data link or transport layers.
- Flow control: transport layer (e.g., TCP)
- Segmentation: transport layer (breaking data into segments)
- Multiplexing:transport layer function (combining multiple signals)
`},{id:13,type:"radio",title:"Who gets this?",question:"The TCP header specifies which value to ensure that data is processed by the correct application",options:["Port","Sequence Number","Window Size","Source IP Address","MAC Address","Protocol Number","Checksum","TTL (Time To Live)"],answer:"Port"},{id:15,type:"radio",title:"Node-on-node action",question:"Which layer of the OSI model is responsible for node-to-node data delivery and framing",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],answer:"Data Link Layer"},{id:16,type:"radio",title:"Choose your weapon",question:"Which device or service operates at the Data Link Layer to manage node-to-node communication",options:["switch","router","hub","firewall","repeater","bridge","modem"],answer:"switch"},{id:17,type:"radio",title:"LLC purpose",question:"What is the purpose of the Logical Link Control (LLC) sub-layer in the Data Link Layer",options:["It defines the physical addressing method for nodes","It manages communication with the network layer protocols","It is responsible for error detection and correction","It converts data from bits into electrical signals"],answer:"It manages communication with the network layer protocols"},{id:18,type:"radio",title:"Physical layer magic",question:"What is a key distinction of the components at the physical layer of the OSI model",options:["They use software to process data","They involve encoding and signaling to transmit data","They define the routing paths for data across networks","They are responsible for application protocols like HTTP"],answer:"They involve encoding and signaling to transmit data"},{id:19,type:"radio",title:"Not mine",question:"Which of the following is **NOT** a responsibility of the Data Link Layer",options:["Adding physical addresses to data","Error detection and retransmission","Framing data for transmission","Routing data between different networks"],answer:"Routing data between different networks",description:"The Data Link Layer focuses on node-to-node communication within the same network — things like adding physical addresses, framing, handling error detection and retransmission."},{id:20,type:"radio",title:"Bits to circuit",question:"In the OSI model, which layer is responsible for transforming data from bits into electrical signals for transmission",options:["Physical Layer","Data Link Layer","Network Layer","Transport Layer","Session Layer","Presentation Layer","Application Layer"],answer:"Physical Layer"}];export{e as default};
